{
    "subject": "resource/Netviewer",
    "predicate": "property/location",
    "object": "Karlsruhe,",
    "human_readable": "The location of Netviewer is Karlsruhe.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8071724772453308,
            "question": "Where is Netviewer located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6713110208511353,
            "question": "In which country is Netviewer situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6158076524734497,
            "question": "What city is Netviewer in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5414890646934509,
            "question": "What is the location of Netviewer's headquarters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47670698165893555,
            "question": "Is Netviewer located in a major European city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4728027880191803,
            "question": "Netviewer is based in which German city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3442535102367401,
            "question": "Is Netviewer based in Germany?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3305615186691284,
            "question": "If you wanted to visit Netviewer, what city would you go to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32100915908813477,
            "question": "Can you name a city associated with Netviewer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22538231313228607,
            "question": "What is the address of Netviewer's office?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The location of Netviewer is Karlsruhe.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6514_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a city associated with Netviewer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6514_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you wanted to visit Netviewer, what city would you go to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6514_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Netviewer based in Germany?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6514_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6514_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6514_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6514_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6514_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6514_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6514_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6514_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6514_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6514_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6514_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have more triples to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information provided confirms that Netviewer's office is indeed located in Karlsruhe, Germany. This is stated explicitly in several documents, including file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6514/re-ranker-msmarco/7.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6514/re-ranker-msmarco/22.txt."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe query \"The location of Netviewer is Karlsruhe.\" is supported by the documents, which state that \"Netviewer is located in Karlsruhe, Germany.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}